# **Adam Sackfield**

# <u>adamsackfield.uk</u> <u>github.com/adampaulsackfield</u>

#### **PROFILE**

I like to build things, whether that involves hardware (from the Raspberry Pi to Dell server racks) or the software that makes the hardware do things. My passion for learning has given me a broad range of knowledge across multiple disciplines. Currently I have been studying Full-Stack JavaScript at NorthCoders, whilst continuing my role as a Technical Specialist for Apple which has given me many transferrable skills.

#### **BACKGROUND**

On my journey I have had the pleasure to work with some amazing technologies, including:

- NodeJS Creating APIs, Projects Generators and Servers
- Express A framework for NodeJS for quickly building out servers.
- MongoDB / SQL Modelling data and serving that data through APIs
- ReactJS Client side framework for building web apps.
- Jest Test Driven Development

## **SKILLS**

I have a very good understanding of JavaScript and the most popular frameworks. Alongside JavaScript I have a limited knowledge of C, Python and Ruby. My approach to development is Test Driven and following industry best practices. I have experience in building out Full-Stack applications either solo as or part of a team, using agile methodologies and version control systems.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Coding Bootcamp Student, NorthCoders, Manchester -2022-present

- Industry-led curriculum, covering some of the top JavaScript frameworks
- Taught best practices throughout, including version control, collaboration, Test Driven Development and pair programming
- Personal Portfolio Built using ReactJS, Sanity.io and TailwindCSS
  - Hosted using Netlify and Sanity.io adamsackfield.uk

- GitHub <a href="https://github.com/adampaulsackfield/portfolio">https://github.com/adampaulsackfield/portfolio</a>
- Full Stack Project NC News Built using NodeJS, ExpressJS, SQL and React.
  - Hosted using Heroku and Netlify https://neon-froyo-ab23ec.netlify.app/
  - GitHub -
    - Front-End: <a href="https://github.com/adampaulsackfield/NC-news-fe">https://github.com/adampaulsackfield/NC-news-fe</a>
    - Back-End: https://github.com/adampaulsackfield/nc-news-sql

## Technical Specialist, Apple, Manchester — 2019-present

- Taking appointments at the Genius Bar
- Interact with propriety diagnostics software
- Quickly asses and categorise issues
- Present the customer with a resolution or options
- Makes decisions using the tools provided using best judgement and positive intent
- Managing the Genius Bar: checking in with customers, taking adequate notes and liaising with other parts of the store to ensure efficiency

# Personal Assistant, Travel Counsellors, Manchester -2012-2019

- Diary management
- Making calls, scheduling meetings and flights
- Note taking, live and from dictation
- Letter writing, errand running and general technical support

### **EDUCATION**

Coney Green High School - 9 GCSEs

Since leaving high school, like all humans I am learning and teaching myself daily. I am curious by nature and thus spend a lot of time intrigued by new technologies and spend time breaking things, followed by even more time fixing them.

Manchester, England 077137 37666 adam@adamsackfield.uk